Warning. Player violated the rules.
Bystander's Silence penalty
mechanism activated.
You pieced it together pretty fast.
Dr. Xiao.
Because someone stopped the car
from hitting us.
The highest place. If I get a perfect
score, I can go to the highest place.
Let's go.
The door is locked from the outside.
What's wrong with him?
Should we look for medicine?
There's no medicine. There's nothing.
It's not a disease.
It's hyperventilation caused
by an acute panic attack.
His psychological trauma of being
locked up and abandoned
has manifested here as claustrophobia
and suffocation.
Looking for medicine is useless.
If we can't find the lethal evidence
that triggered his trauma,
he will suffocate himself to death.
On the 14th, signed the divorce agreement.
On the 15th, wrote the letter
of commitment.
The closet is empty.
The drag marks of the suitcase
are very clear on the floor.
This is not a reward at all.
They completely moved out
and abandoned him that day.
There's no need for him to see this.
Warning. Key clues are being destroyed.
There's only a pile of garbage
in this room.
No clues.
This guy is getting more
and more empathetic.
Dear visitors,
there are only five minutes left
until the park closes.
Parents, please lead your children out
of the park as soon as possible.
After closing,
all children who haven't been picked up
will stay in the park forever.
No, I don't want to stay here.
I don't want to stay here.
Pang.
Mom, Dad.
I'm here.
Come pick me up.
Why did I get a perfect score,
I pieced the test paper together,
and got every question right,
but you still won't take me?
You need to be sensible.
Mom and Dad are very busy.
Don't keep pestering us.
We'll talk about it next time you do well.
If you keep banging, you'll really die.
Look back.
Look at us.
You don't understand.
They promised to pick me up at 5:30.
I've always been obedient.
I endured everything.
I didn't make a fuss
or spend money recklessly.
I didn't cause them any trouble.
I did it all.
So what am I still lacking?
It was never your fault.
They never intended to pick you up.
No.
This is not fair.
Even if the clocks here weren't
stuck at 5:30 forever,
they wouldn't come.
It's because I'm not good enough.
It's not that you're not good enough.
It's that they don't deserve
to be parents.
This is a scam destined
to have no one waiting for you.
You are torturing yourself
with other people's mistakes.
Now,
cut off the rotten flesh.
Stop waiting.
Did you hear what Han said?
Stop waiting for them.
There are still five of us
on this broken car.
Let's go. We'll take you out of the park.
Yes, we'll take you out.
We'll leave the park together.
Congratulations, tourists.
You've perfectly cleared the third stop,
Childhood Dream Amusement Park.
Five went in,
five came out.
We did it.
Nether Mortuary,
Huang Kai's obsession with his late wife.
Ghost Empress's Palace, Chen Qiang's
obsession with power and control.
Innocence Amusement Park,
Pang's obsession with
a complete childhood.
Every stop
is manifested from
the inner demons of one of us.
So whose turn will it be next?
I have no obsessions.
What about you, Xiao Han?
What is
your obsession?
Take a guess.
One wrong step across the boundary
of life and death,
how can I bear my misplaced kindness?
Pity the broken soul,
blood staining the long street,
with nowhere to cry out.
Beating the loud drum to claim a life.